Hello everyone, it's Aline. Welcome to another video here on my channel.
This one is an outfit styling idea video with the new Paradise bodysuits.
Because they do not only have leggings like this one, but they also have bodysuits.
And I thought about some different stylings and I'm going to show them to you. So enjoy!
Oh, by the way, I think I didn't show you these leggings yet. They're new. They're launched in December. Also a silver version. And it's the classic leggings from Paradise, you know. But yeah, actually I wanted to show you the bodysuit, so let's move on.
First outfit of this video. There are three paradise products in this look. Can you spot them? I give you a hint. One, two, three.
so there are a couple of things I want to point out about this look I think it's a really great
look by the way I would totally go out like that and go into the city like that have a drink
maybe go to work without a belt though I just love my shoes all right the bodysuit it's a
four-leather look in the front but on the back it is fabric like really stretchy fabric
which has a really big plus point it's comfy for me although I'm really long so the back side is
really stretchy and the bodysuit kind of yeah morphs into the shape you need so I have no
problems here with the length which is a really big plus then we have the skort also a new paradise
product it's a skirt but it's also short because now you can see that uh yeah it's a panty which
is integrated so it's sewn onto the skirt also really handy and then we have the tights here
they look like your average normal bitsy throat hides but they're super cozy
because they're lined with fleece they keep you really warm also in winter but
they do not look like it so I'm going to show you a short clip from the inside
something else I can add is this leather jacket now it feels kind of complete
because I'm not used to the sleeveless options and tops but with the leather jacket I feel
more in my element and it is kind of
a look that fits 100% in my wardrobe in my style. If you're like me and you prefer long sleeve
bodysuits and tops then let's move on to the next one because it's basically the same one but
with long arms this is the long sleeve version and I just love it because it fits also really
good and the arms are really long I had to say that I paired it with a simple black paradise
aesthetic pants so from the front it's four letter look also with the match heels I mean
from the back it's not the faux leather completely because of the fabric we have here again in
the back of the bodysuit but it's also really comfy and I think I wanted to create a look
with it and this is just a bit plain so I'm going to add some really cool accessories
Okay, so this is what I call a cool look.
I really like this and I don't know how often I used the necklace or the belt within the
last few months since I bought them in London from Nowhere Designs, but they are just so
handy and complimentary when it comes to spicing up the outfits.
So, I love this.
Now I just need a bag and then I could go shopping. By the way shopping when they launched the bodysuit. So when Paradise launched the bodysuit in December it took like two or three days and it was sold out.
So they were gone really fast and I was happy to have one. And now they just restocked them so I can order them again. And not only this one but they also launched it in the ultra version. So PVC bodysuit with long arms.
And also since this is a thermal version, so we have a bit of the thick fabric here, they launched the additional light version with the same fabric as the normal pants are made of. If you have any Paradise products you know what I'm talking about. Otherwise have a look at the homepage.
so I tried the jacket in the first look but let's see how it looks with the
leggings together
yep also works I think this is also cool way if it's too cool I just put on a
leather jacket and then you're good to go
Nice!
I'm not going to switch into the next bodysuit just now.
I first want to show you a variation for this one.
Second option I wanted to show you with this bodysuit, a kind of more casual look.
And it reminds me a bit of techwear. It's not really techwear, there are a lot of accessories and stuff missing.
It's not practical enough, but with the cargo pants and the boots, it's kind of a cool look.
I still need more cool cargo pants, so if you have any tips on cool cargo pants, hit me up in the comments section.
Next up is the red PVC bodysuit, and I bet you cannot guess what's coming.
Last but not least, this ultra cherry bodysuit.
and I thought long and hard about what kind of look I want to create with it
because of course you can just use it as a normal top and pair it with the jeans
or leggings but I thought well let's go all in and I created this look I think
it's a mashup between like a superhero outfit and gymnastics look and and it's
really bold of course the color combination but also the materials I
mean this is PVC again but the backside is also fabric so I paired it with a
pair of tights in the same fabric but in black and red shoes and the black gloves
and I don't know where you would wear that to this outfit maybe a Finnish party
maybe a motto party but I think it's a fun look so that was my goal here to create a look and not
just some bodysuit and some leggings again or I mean you could also pair it which I saw the red
bodysuit and the red leggings that is also a cool combination but I wanted to do something different
something nobody showed before I think this is a really fun outfit I have to look in the mirror
all the time because it's also so unusual this color combination it's really kind of old school
with the black and red okay i wanted to do a selfie but one disadvantage with the gloss is i can't
tap on my screen i heard that you can do it with your nose and it works
it's not working oh it's a video stop so normally you can see the selfies first on my patreon
if you want to see all the behind the scenes and most of the photo shoots I do
first head over there and check it out anyway don't forget to use my discount
code on all the paradise products you get 10% off with my name Celine and of
course I'll link everything down below but I hope you enjoyed this video and
you could take some inspiration with you maybe not this outfit but the other ones
before I think they were quite cool so see you around in the next video have a nice day bye